<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cypheron</string>
    <string name="title">cypheron</string>
    <string name="encrypt_tab">Encrypt</string>
    <string name="decrypt_tab">Decrypt</string>


    <string name="tab1_text1">Select Cipher</string>
    <string name="enter_text">Enter Text Here</string>
    <string name="key">Enter Key</string>
    <string name="en_tx">Encrypted Text</string>
    <string name="de_tx">Decrypted Text</string>


    <string name="help_fragment">Help fragment</string>
    <string name="restart_text">reset application</string>
    <string name="restart_button">reset</string>
    <string name="dark">enable dark mode</string>


    <string name="mono">Monoalphabetic Cipher</string>
    <string name="help_mono">A monoalphabetic substitution cipher,
        also known as a simple substitution cipher, relies on a fixed replacement structure.
        That is, the substitution is fixed for each letter of the alphabet. Thus, if "a" is
        encrypted to "R", then every time we see the letter "a" in the plaintext, we replace it
        with the letter "R" in the ciphertext.</string>

    <string name="caes">Ceasar Cipher</string>
    <string name="help_caes">Caesar cipher, also the shift cipher, Caesar code or Caesar shift,
        is one of the simplest and most widely known encryption techniques. It is a type of
        substitution cipher in which each letter in the plaintext is replaced by a letter some
        fixed number of positions down the alphabet. For example, with a left shift of 3, D would
        be replaced by A, E would become B, and so on. The method is named after Julius Caesar,
        who used it in his private correspondence</string>

    <string name="at">Atbash Cipher</string>
    <string name="help_atb"> Atbash cipher is a substitution cipher with just one specific key
        where all the letters are reversed that is A to Z and Z to A. It was originally used to
        encode the Hebrew alphabets but it can be modified to encode any alphabet.</string>

    <string name="ver">Vernam Cipher</string>
    <string name="help_vern">Vernam Cipher is a method of encrypting alphabetic text. It is one
        of the Transposition techniques for converting a plain text into a cipher text. In this
        mechanism we assign a number to each character of the Plain-Text,
        like (a = 0, b = 1, c = 2, … z = 25). </string>

    <string name="aes">AES Cipher</string>
    <string name="help_aes">AES is an iterative rather than Feistel cipher. It is based on
        ‘substitution–permutation network’. It comprises of a series of linked operations,
        some of which involve replacing inputs by specific outputs (substitutions) and others
        involve shuffling bits around (permutations).</string>

    <string name="rail">Rail Fence Cipher</string>
    <string name="help_rail">The rail fence cipher (sometimes called zigzag cipher) is a
        transposition cipher that jumbles up the order of the letters of a message using a
        basic algorithm.The rail fence cipher works by writing your message on alternate lines
        across the page, and then reading off each line in turn.</string>

    <string name="see_link_for_detail">Click here for detail</string>


    <string name="about">Developed By Vaibhav Pawar <br/>
        T.Y B.Sc (C.S) Roll No 747<br/>
        Patkar-Varde College<br/>
        2020-2021<br/>
    </string>

    <string name="version">version 1.0.0</string>

</resources>